https://www.jorvet.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Policies for Jorgensen Labs, Inc website:
PRIVACY POLICY:
“We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.”
SECURITY POLICY
“Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.”
REFUND POLICY
All orders will be considered complete unless we are notified within 24 hours of receipt of shipment.  All returned goods will have a 20% restocking charge.  All returned goods must have a returned goods authorization (RGA) number.  Please call customer service at 800-525-5614  to obtain an RGA number.  Boxes not marked with an RGA # or  marked with an expired RGA # will be returned to sender.  All items returned for warranty repair/replacement must be accompanied by a copy of the invoice showing the purchase. All refunds will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase within ten (10) business days after we receive your returned merchandise.  Original Shipping Fees are not refundable.
Shipping Policy/Delivery Policy
Most orders  will ship out within four days of purchase. We may determine the most efficient shipping carrier for you order. The carriers that may be used are: U.S. Postal Service (USPS), United Parcel Service (UPS) or FedEx.
Shipments to P.O. Boxes must be sent  via U S Postal Service.
If you’re trying to estimate when a package will be delivered, please note the following:
Credit card authorization and verification must be received prior to packaging and shipping.
Federal Express and UPS deliveries occur Monday through Friday, Excluding holidays.
If you require same day shipment, overnight shipment, or any  form of express  shipping, please confirm by calling 1-800-525-5614 for charges.  All same day out orders will be charged a additional $10 handling fee.joel
Over five decades of providing high quality veterinary specialty instruments and animal health products
We are experiencing Technical Difficulties With Our Checkout Process.
Sorry For Any Inconvenience This May Cause & We Are Working Diligently To Resolve This ASAP Dismiss
